[
  {
    "question": "How many minutes do we try a land line that hanged up a 9-1-1 call?",
    "choices": ["3 minutes", "1 minute", "5 minutes", "2 minutes"],
    "answer": "3 minutes",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the standard 9-1-1 line greeting?",
    "choices": [
      "Orange County 9-1-1, what is your emergency?",
      "Orange County 9-1-1, what is the address of your emergency? (Repeat, unless it matches ALI.)",
      "What is the address of your emergency?",
      "This is Orange County 9-1-1, how can I help you?"
    ],
    "answer": "Orange County 9-1-1, what is the address of your emergency? (Repeat, unless it matches ALI.)",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 2nd question in the 9-1-1 call process?",
    "choices": [
      "What's your name?",
      "What's the phone number you are calling from? (Repeat, unless it matches ANI. Say VERIFIED if it matches.)",
      "Okay, tell me exactly what happened.",
      "Where is your emergency?"
    ],
    "answer": "What's the phone number you are calling from? (Repeat, unless it matches ANI. Say VERIFIED if it matches.)",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 3rd question in the 9-1-1 call process?",
    "choices": [
      "What is your location?",
      "What's your name?",
      "What is your emergency?",
      "Can you describe what happened?"
    ],
    "answer": "What's your name?",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 4th question in the 9-1-1 call process?",
    "choices": [
      "What's your name?",
      "Okay, tell me exactly what happened.",
      "What is your phone number?",
      "Where are you?"
    ],
    "answer": "Okay, tell me exactly what happened.",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who can you use the Aspirin tool on?",
    "choices": [
      "Anyone over 18 years old",
      "Patient is functionally alert, 16 years of age or older, no reported stroke symptoms, and not pregnant.",
      "Patients with chest pain over age 21",
      "Any adult not allergic to aspirin"
    ],
    "answer": "Patient is functionally alert, 16 years of age or older, no reported stroke symptoms, and not pregnant.",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the 5 W's?",
    "choices": [
      "WHERE, WHO, WHY, WHAT, WHEN",
      "WHEN, WHERE, WHAT, WHO, WEAPONS",
      "WHERE, WHEN, WHAT, WHO, WEAPONS",
      "WHAT, WHO, WHEN, WEAPONS, WHY"
    ],
    "answer": "WHERE, WHEN, WHAT, WHO, WEAPONS",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the standard alarm / non-emergency / administrative line greeting?",
    "choices": [
      "Orange County 9-1-1, what is your emergency?",
      "Orange County Communications, this is [... YOUR NAME ...]",
      "This is the non-emergency line, state your concern.",
      "Orange County Services, how may I assist?"
    ],
    "answer": "Orange County Communications, this is [... YOUR NAME ...]",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a DOMESTIC?",
    "choices": [
      "Natural body of water",
      "Water tank or canal",
      "Man made structure e.g., pool, hot tub, bathtub",
      "Any body of water used recreationally"
    ],
    "answer": "Man made structure e.g., pool, hot tub, bathtub",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a SPECIALIZED?",
    "choices": [
      "Private backyard pool",
      "Natural setting or man-made structure not intended for domestic use e.g., lake, river, canal, water tank.",
      "Bathtub or hot tub in home",
      "Public swimming pool"
    ],
    "answer": "Natural setting or man-made structure not intended for domestic use e.g., lake, river, canal, water tank.",
    "category": "OTHER"
  },
  {
    "question": "Abdominal Pains / Problems",
    "answer": "ABDO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Allergies / Envenomations (Stings/Bites)",
    "answer": "ALLE",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Animal Bites / Attacks",
    "answer": "ANIB",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Back Pain",
    "answer": "BACK",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Breathing Problems",
    "answer": "BREA",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Burns (Scalds) / Explosion (Blast)",
    "answer": "BURN",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Carbon Monoxide / Inhalation / HAZMAT",
    "answer": "CARBMO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cardiac or Respiratory Arrest / Death",
    "answer": "CARD",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chest Pain / Chest Discomfort",
    "answer": "CHEST",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choking",
    "answer": "CHOK",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convulsions / Seizures",
    "answer": "CONV",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Diabetic Problems",
    "answer": "DIAB",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drowning",
    "answer": "DROWN",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrocution / Lightning",
    "answer": "ELEC",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Eye Problems / Injuries",
    "answer": "EYEP",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Falls",
    "answer": "FALLS",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Headache",
    "answer": "HEAD",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heart Problems / A.I.C.D.",
    "answer": "HEPR",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heat / Cold Exposure",
    "answer": "HECO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hemorrhage (Bleeding) / Lacerations",
    "answer": "HEMO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Overdose / Poisoning (Ingestion)",
    "answer": "OVER",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pregnancy / Childbirth / Miscarriage",
    "answer": "PREG",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sick Person (Specific Diagnosis)",
    "answer": "SICK",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Impalement / Penetrating Trauma",
    "answer": "IMPALE",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Self-Inflicted GSW / Stab",
    "answer": "STABSI",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stroke / Transient Ischemic Attack (TIA)",
    "answer": "STROKE",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traffic Collision / Transportation Incident (with Injury)",
    "answer": "MVCPI",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traumatic Injuries (Specific)",
    "answer": "TRAU",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unconscious / Fainting (Near)",
    "answer": "UNCO",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transfer / Interfacility / Palliative Care",
    "answer": "TIPC",
    "category": "EMD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aircraft Emergency",
    "answer": "AIRC",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alarms",
    "answer": "ALARFI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Citizen Assist / Service Call",
    "answer": "FIASST",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Confined Space / Structure Collapse",
    "answer": "CONFSP",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrical Hazard",
    "answer": "ELEHAZ",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Elevator / Escalator Rescue",
    "answer": "ELEVATR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Explosion",
    "answer": "EXPLOS",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Extrication / Entrapped (Machinery, Vehicle - Non MVC",
    "answer": "ENTRAP",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fuel Spill / Fuel Odor",
    "answer": "FUELSP",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gas Leak / Gas Odor (Natural or LP Gas)",
    "answer": "GASLEA",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "HAZMAT",
    "answer": "HAZM",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "High Angle Rescue (Above or Below Grade)",
    "answer": "HIANGL",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lightning Strike (Investigation)",
    "answer": "LIGHTN",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marine Fire / Boat Fire",
    "answer": "BOATFI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mutual Aid / Assist Outside Agency",
    "answer": "MUTF",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Odor (Strange / Unknown)",
    "answer": "ODORIN",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Outside Fire",
    "answer": "OUTFIR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Smoke Investigation (Outside)",
    "answer": "SMOINV",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Structure Fire",
    "answer": "STRUCT",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Train and Rail Collision / Derailment",
    "answer": "TRAINC",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vehicle Fire",
    "answer": "VEHI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Water / Ice / Mud Rescue",
    "answer": "WATRES",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Watercraft in Distress / Collision",
    "answer": "WATERC",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Train and Rail Fire",
    "answer": "TRAINF",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motor Vehicle Collision",
    "answer": "MVCFI",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Outside Tank Fire (Use 67)",
    "answer": "OUTFIR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sinking Vehicle / Vehicle in Floodwater",
    "answer": "WATRES",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vegetation / Wildland / Brush / Grass Fire (Use 67)",
    "answer": "OUTFIR",
    "category": "EFD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Abduction (Kidnapping) / Custodial Abduction / Custody Issue / Hostage Situation",
    "answer": "ABDUCT",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Abuse / Abandonment / Neglect",
    "answer": "ABUSE",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Administrative (Lost or Found Property, Found Unexploded Ordinance)",
    "answer": "ADMIN",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alarms (Police)",
    "answer": "ALARLE",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Animal",
    "answer": "ANIM",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assault / Sexual Assault / Shooting / Stabbing",
    "answer": "ASLT",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Assist Other Agencies",
    "answer": "LEASST",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bomb Found / Suspicious Package (Letter, Item) / Product Contamination",
    "answer": "SUSPAC",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bomb Threat",
    "answer": "BOMB",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Burglary (Break-and-Enter / Home Invasion)",
    "answer": "BUBE",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Damage / Vandalism / Mischief",
    "answer": "DAMA",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Disturbance / Nuissance",
    "answer": "DIST",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Domestic Disturbance / Violence",
    "answer": "DOME",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Driving Under the Influence",
    "answer": "DUI",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drugs",
    "answer": "DRUGS",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fraud / Forgery",
    "answer": "FRAUD",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Harassment / Stalking / Threats",
    "answer": "HARA",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Indecency / Lewdness",
    "answer": "INDEC",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mental Disorder (Behavioral Problems)",
    "answer": "MENDIS",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Miscellaneous",
    "answer": "MISC",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Missing / Runaway / Found Person",
    "answer": "MISS",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Officer Needs Assistance",
    "answer": "OFFNA",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Public Service (Lock-out / Lock-In, Peace, Welfare Check, Reckless Activity)",
    "answer": "PUBLIC",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Robbery / Carjacking",
    "answer": "ROBBER",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suicidal Person / Attempted Suicide",
    "answer": "SUIC",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suspicious / Wanted (Person, Circumstances, Vehicle)",
    "answer": "SUSPIC",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Theft (Larceny)",
    "answer": "THEFT",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traffic Collision / Transportation Incident, Stuck Accelerator",
    "answer": "MVCLE",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traffic Violation / Complaint / Hazard",
    "answer": "TRFHAZ",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Treaspassing / Unwanted",
    "answer": "TRES",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unknown (3rd Party)",
    "answer": "UNKNLE",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Weapons / Firearms",
    "answer": "WEAPON",
    "category": "EPD"
  },
  {
    "question": "Active Assailant (Shooter)",
    "answer": "ACTIVE",
    "category": "EPD"
  }
]
